Hi, Mr. President.
I'm honored being here today,
and I first wanted to start by thanking you guys
for designating Antifa a terrorist group.
It's exactly what this group is.
It's a long time coming.
I'm an investigative journalist from Seattle.
I worked for the Postmillennial alongside Andy Ngo
and Jack Posobiec.
I have been infiltrating Antifa cells
in Seattle and Portland for the past decade.
I know their inner workings,
and Antifa uses extreme political violence
to crush the civil rights of their political enemies
and believes that violence is justified
by any means necessary.
But today, I want to focus on what is happening
in Portland at the ICE facility.
I've been covering this for the past four months,
and this is a call out to corporate media
who has completely ignored this story
or has falsely reported on it.
This is nothing short other than a sustained attack
on the United States,
which is being supported by Democratic elected officials.
The Portland Police Bureau
has completely abandoned several blocks
outside the ICE facility,
giving away their jurisdiction to a terrorist group
who has spent the past four months harassing,
assaulting, and intimidating anyone they perceive
to be against their cause.
Not only have federal agents been relentlessly assaulted
for more than 100 consecutive days,
black clad anarchist militants
concealing their identities behind black facial coverings
have been assaulting reporters
just for trying to cover their crimes.
Today, I am sitting here with a black eye and a concussion
after being violently hit in the face with a metal pole
while reporting outside the ICE facility
just this past week.
After the attack, I immediately went
to three Portland police officers
who refused to detain the suspect.
I took the time to chase down the suspect
in the streets, had her held for 35 minutes.